

# KAYLA HORN

#### **PROFILE**

I am an enthusiastic and ambitious young professional, seeking career opportunities to expand my knowledge in the business world. For the past six years, I have held various leadership roles in customer service positions, orchestrating and controlling inventory. I have provided marketing and digital transformation consultative services to Fortune 1000 Retail Marketing Executives. I have gained experience with Tableau, SPSS, Google Analytics, GoogleAdWords, Microsoft Suite, GoogleSuite, and Salesforce.

When I am not on the job, I love staying active and exploring new places; Whether it is hiking, biking or running, count me in! I also have a hidden talent for making breakfast foods.

#### CONTACT

#### PHONE:

262-402-7539

#### WEBSITE:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kaylahorn-828280146/

#### **EMAIL:**

Kahorn15@aol.com

## **EDUCATION**

#### University of Wisconsin Eau Claire (Sep 2015 – May 2019)

- → B.A.- General Marketing (Cum Lade)
- → Business Communications Certificate
- → College of Business Dean's List
- → Lorraine Missling Scholarship

Experience with Tableau, SPSS, Google Analytics, GoogleAdWords and Microsoft Suite, GoogleSuite, and Salesforce

Germantown High School (Sep 2011 – Jun 2015)

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Held various Retail/ Customer Service Positions** 6 years of bartending & serving experience

2013-Present

Most recent...

- → Harp Irish Pub: Milwaukee, WI
  - Bartender & Server (May 2019- Present)
- → Mogies Pub: Eau Claire, WI -Bartender & Server (March 2017- May 2019)

#### Client Services, Marketing Solutions Intern

May-Aug 2017

Quad Graphics: Sussex, WI

- → Supported a Retail Management Consultant Team
- → Provided Marketing and Digital Transformation Consultative Services to Fortune 1000 Retail Marketing Executives
- → Assisted clients in redefining their brands and organizations to meet the rapid changes in customer's expectations
- → Helped create lean manufacturing client workflows and swim lanes
- → Constructed client and market profiles
- → Collected and organized customer information and data

# Manager, HPJ Communication Specialists Sep-Dec 2019 (High Impact Advanced Business Communications Class)

- → Interviewed, selected, and managed a team of four advanced business communication students
- → Planned & delivered an interactive, two-session seminar on Business Etiquette
- → Prepared invitations, participation guides, and 20+ page professional manual to support the seminar

### STRENGTHS

Experience with Tableau, SPSS, Google Analytics, GoogleAdWords and Microsoft Suite, GoogleSuite and Salesforce

- → Leadership
- → Teamwork
- → Adaptable
- → Efficient and Effective Communication
- → Active Listener
- → Customer Centric